libertylondongirl.com 2019-05-31

# THE LLG PRIVACY POLICY - Liberty London Girl

Your privacy is important to us.

It is our policy here at LibertyLondonGirl to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. Accordingly, we have developed this privacy policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and otherwise make use of personal information.

We have outlined our privacy policy below.

We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual.

We do not use your information for marketing purposes unless you actively sign up to our newsletter.

We will collect and use personal information solely for fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other ancillary purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.

Personal data we collect is relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, we make all efforts to ensure the data is accurate, complete, and up-to-date.

We will protect personal information by using reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We will only retain personal information for as long as necessary for the fulfilment of those purposes unless required by law.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. LibertyLondonGirl may make changes to this policy from time to time at our sole discretion.

From 25th May 2018, the law will be changing on how we handle personal data. LibertyLondonGirl is committed to making sure your data is kept safe and in accordance with GDPR.
